{"sid": "MGLB0P2JENWY_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 333766, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 333767, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 353126]], "time_left_end": "281", "answered_time": 353126, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "281", "question_time_start": 353126, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["calc_3", 357006], ["calc_4", 357758], ["calc_+", 358654], ["calc_8", 359302], ["calc_7", 359678], ["calc_3", 360157], ["calc_=", 360652], ["submit", 367248]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 367248, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 367249, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 374280]], "time_left_end": "260", "answered_time": 374280, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "260", "question_time_start": 374280, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 379423]], "time_left_end": "255", "answered_time": 379423, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "255", "question_time_start": 379423, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 384493]], "time_left_end": "250", "answered_time": 384493, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "250", "question_time_start": 384493, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["calc_7", 389093], ["calc_8", 389384], ["calc_+", 390100], ["calc_3", 391598], ["calc_7", 392232], ["calc_+", 393281], ["calc_2", 393904], ["calc_3", 394222], ["calc_+", 395086], ["calc_4", 395685], ["calc_7", 396070], ["calc_=", 396811], ["submit", 401493]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "233", "answered_time": 401493, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "233", "question_time_start": 401493, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 410193]], "time_left_end": "224", "answered_time": 410193, "user_answer": "193", "user_correct": "False", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "224", "question_time_start": 410193, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 414051]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 414051, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 414051, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 421298]], "time_left_end": "213", "answered_time": 421298, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "213", "question_time_start": 421298, "question": "47+17", "correct_answer": 64, "events": [["submit", 425169]], "time_left_end": "209", "answered_time": 425169, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 425170, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "209", "question_time_start": 425170, "question": "17+697", "correct_answer": 714, "events": [["submit", 435178]], "time_left_end": "199", "answered_time": 435178, "user_answer": "714", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "199", "question_time_start": 435178, "question": "4+88+24", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 441799]], "time_left_end": "192", "answered_time": 441799, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "192", "question_time_start": 441799, "question": "7+4+8+48", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 448895]], "time_left_end": "185", "answered_time": 448895, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "185", "question_time_start": 448895, "question": "73+58+37+36", "correct_answer": 204, "events": [["submit", 464305]], "time_left_end": "170", "answered_time": 464305, "user_answer": "204", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "170", "question_time_start": 464305, "question": "98+148", "correct_answer": 246, "events": [["submit", 471241]], "time_left_end": "163", "answered_time": 471241, "user_answer": "146", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "163", "question_time_start": 471242, "question": "13+98", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 483497]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 483497, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 483498, "question": "7+66+39", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 493922]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 493922, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 493922, "question": "6+78+66", "correct_answer": 150, "events": [["submit", 499730]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 499730, "user_answer": "150", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 499730, "question": "3+9+9+28", "correct_answer": 49, "events": [["submit", 506162]], "time_left_end": "128", "answered_time": 506162, "user_answer": "49", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "128", "question_time_start": 506162, "question": "56+76", "correct_answer": 132, "events": [["submit", 509193]], "time_left_end": "125", "answered_time": 509193, "user_answer": "132", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 509193, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "125", "question_time_start": 509194, "question": "3+54+84", "correct_answer": 141, "events": [["submit", 517177]], "time_left_end": "117", "answered_time": 517177, "user_answer": "141", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "117", "question_time_start": 517178, "question": "3+3+4+66", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 520133]], "time_left_end": "114", "answered_time": 520133, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "114", "question_time_start": 520133, "question": "38+59+89+28", "correct_answer": 214, "events": [["calc_3", 526346], ["calc_8", 526822], ["calc_+", 527936], ["calc_5", 528366], ["calc_9", 528994], ["calc_+", 529454], ["calc_8", 529918], ["calc_9", 530360], ["calc_+", 531046], ["calc_2", 531582], ["calc_8", 532101], ["calc_=", 532702], ["submit", 537505]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "97", "answered_time": 537505, "user_answer": "214", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "97", "question_time_start": 537506, "question": "13+327", "correct_answer": 340, "events": [["submit", 540706]], "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 540706, "user_answer": "340", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 540706, "question": "47+26", "correct_answer": 73, "events": [["submit", 545042]], "time_left_end": "89", "answered_time": 545042, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "89", "question_time_start": 545042, "question": "7+3+3+96", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 548834]], "time_left_end": "85", "answered_time": 548834, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "85", "question_time_start": 548834, "question": "9+76+57", "correct_answer": 142, "events": [["submit", 557929]], "time_left_end": "76", "answered_time": 557929, "user_answer": "172", "user_correct": "False", "score": "21"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "76", "question_time_start": 557930, "question": "57+819", "correct_answer": 876, "events": [["submit", 572433]], "time_left_end": "62", "answered_time": 572433, "user_answer": "876", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "62", "question_time_start": 572434, "question": "7+33+19", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 574906]], "time_left_end": "59", "answered_time": 574906, "user_answer": "49", "user_correct": "False", "score": "21"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "59", "question_time_start": 574906, "question": "43+57", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 582194]], "time_left_end": "52", "answered_time": 582194, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 582194, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "52", "question_time_start": 582194, "question": "83+333", "correct_answer": 416, "events": [["submit", 592854]], "time_left_end": "41", "answered_time": 592854, "user_answer": "416", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "41", "question_time_start": 592854, "question": "29+18", "correct_answer": 47, "events": [["submit", 599049]], "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 599049, "user_answer": "47", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 599049, "question": "7+8+4+38", "correct_answer": 57, "events": [["submit", 604737]], "time_left_end": "30", "answered_time": 604737, "user_answer": "57", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "30", "question_time_start": 604738, "question": "4+16+96", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 613993]], "time_left_end": "20", "answered_time": 613993, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "20", "question_time_start": 613993, "question": "6+54+36", "correct_answer": 96, "events": [["submit", 616666]], "time_left_end": "18", "answered_time": 616666, "user_answer": "86", "user_correct": "False", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "18", "question_time_start": 616667, "question": "6+89+99", "correct_answer": 194, "events": []}}}}}